(Beverley:)I'm just not sure it's appropriate
with my son's roommate.
(Sheldon:)Normally, I'd feel the same way.
(Sheldon:)But based on everything
I've observed about us...
(Sheldon:)...I can't help but speculate
we'd be very good together.
(Beverley:)True. I've had a similar observation.
(Beverley:)It's certainly something
I could never do with my husband.
(Sheldon:)I was hesitant the first time I tried it...
(Sheldon:)...but I experienced an unanticipated
and remarkable release of endorphins.
(Sheldon:)- It's quite satisfying.
- Mm.
(Beverley:)I see what you're doing.
(Beverley:)You're appealing
to the neuroscientific researcher in me.
(Sheldon:)You see right through me, don't you?
(Beverley:)Only when you're in a CAT scanner.
[SNORTS THEN LAUGHS]
[BOTH MOANING AND LAUGHING]
(Leonard:)This is actually gonna happen.